This is the one key factor that
separates the best performing videos.
And then after the hook, you want to
actually have a huge drop off and then
you still maintain 100% ICP. Now the
format when it comes to actually
stripping out the videos is actually
extremely intentional. So that's
essentially the structure of your script
and how you follow it. The post
production is extremely important for a
video like this as well. This is [music]
the make or break for the video.
My name is So We Go and these are my
most [music] viral concept pieces broken
down.
All right, this one this one's a fun
one.
>> [music]
[laughter]
[music]
>> Oh, it's such a good feeling. Oh my god.
Generally just so blessed to be in a
situation where I can
make my mom feel happy and feel proud
[music] and
just smile the whole time cracking
jokes. Like it was so amazing.
We did it. We [__] did it.
That has to be one of my favorite reels
of all time. I remember seeing a reel
like this when I was like 16, 17 and I
was like wow, I want to recreate that
one. And so I actually documented that
entire month
and I was able to capture the moment
where I told my mom. And so this was
like one of the most special moments
because I've literally been wanting to
film a video like this for so long and
when the time finally came, it's just
like
wow, such a surreal feeling. The most
Asian mom response ever as well. I'm
probably inspiring a ton of other people
to want to create this video. All right,
so let's break down exactly why this
video performed so well and why the
moment that I saw the video and the post
production all of that, I knew it was
going to pop, right? So essentially this
is a top of funnel video.
And
meaning
this reel was applicable to essentially
the ICP, but also a a general public.
Meaning that my ICP, the the the coach
that's above 30k a month, 100k a month,
300k a month that would want to get good
at content would watch this video, but
then also the general public will watch
this video. And so, what that means is
this is a reel that overlaps this. So,
that reel of making my mom proud is
something that is an overlap between the
ICP and then the dream follower that I
have. And the reason why when you do top
of funnel videos you want to actually
have this overlap is because these
people are the ones that push your video
to more people.
And so again, what is our goal with
content anyways? It's to get as many ICP
leads as possible. Then that means that
in order to get people into our world,
we need to have top of funnel content
that attracts not just the ICP, but the
dream follower because it'll push our
vid out to more people. And to really
break this down, let me give you guys an
example. If
Instagram shows your video to 100
people.
And so instead of the visual hook saying
like, "Oh, you could Pav, you get your
mom's reaction to making 150k a month at
19." If I said, "Hey Pav, you booked 60
calls and generated a record month in
your business. I promise you that video
would probably get like 20k views,
right? And so, the visual hook and
everything appealed to a wider
demographic. So, out of the 100 people,
let's say you know, 85 of them would pay
attention.
And out of that 85 of them, that would
basically tell Instagram that to push
your video to more people, which in turn
leads to more ICP followers. So, a lot
of times people think that oh, if I only
want to attract the qualified ICP, I can
I should only speak to them. But the The
is you need to find that dream follower
that has a wider total addressable
market so that they can push your videos
to attract more of your ICP videos. A
lot of the times the dream follower has
very very similar hobbies and passions
as the ICP. So for example, my dream
follower could be someone that's into
self-improvement. This is someone that
is also wants to make more money. This
is also someone that takes care of his
fitness. And so because this specific
idea and this message in the real appeal
to not just the ICP but a wider
demographic, that's why the video
performed well. And a lot of people get
this wrong because they try to skip
straight into middle of funnel content.
If you skip straight to middle of funnel
content, unless your credibility is
top-notch, nobody will give a [__] about
what you have to say. You have to get
them to actually care about what you
have to say first in order to give them
value or information and get them to
want to listen to you. A lot of the
times
you are going to try and post content to
sign clients and immediately try to skip
this entire step. But again, the reason
why this never actually lands is because
you didn't go through this part first
and you didn't go this part first. And
essentially, you need to create a bank
of top of funnel content that will
essentially check off this box of
admirability so that when you're giving
advice to get to get someone from this
position to that position,
you need to show that you've climbed the
mountain first because when you don't
show the admirability phase, you
essentially look like you're over here.
So when you give value and when you give
information and you wonder why it falls
flat is because they don't look at you
as an enough of a enough as an
authority, which is why lifestyle
content works so well because the
perception is from down up. You need to
make your viewers feel like you've
achieved the dream life, which nine
times out of 10 you actually have unless
you're larping.
Uh and then actually give value and
information and try to shift beliefs.
Because when they look at someone that
they actually admire and respect, that's
when they can actually be influenced and
you're playing a downhill battle, which
is much easier than fighting an uphill
battle. That video was so perfect
because it hit two birds with one stone.
It made me not just admirable because I
achieved an outcome and a dream that a
lot of people want, but it also made me
likable because I showed the
relationship. The one thing I'll say as
well that went into the video was that
it was just extremely authentic. I
wasn't in the mode of like trying to
film a reel. To give you guys context
like back in March, I think this was
Prime trip and yeah, I think this is in
2024 when I was 19 years old, I hit my
first 100k in March. I filmed the entire
month because I knew it was going to be
a big month and so part of that, you
know, entire vlog was a specific segment
of me calling my mom which ended up
being a reel that popped off. If you
want to build a personal brand that
actually feels authentic, then you have
to get out of the frame of mind of like
trying to film everything for short form
and just get in the habit of just
filming it for you. I got into vlogs
because I want to create content that I
can look back on when I'm 30, 40, 50
that I can watch with my kids and be
like, "Yeah, you know, your your dad did
that when he was [__] 19." You know,
that's what I want to do. And so I'm
creating content with a passion and you
can't like that video wasn't forced at
all because I was capturing a very
wholesome moment and I was capturing the
entire month. It felt very genuine
because it was. And so the key point I'm
trying to bring across is that Instagram
shouldn't feel like a performance or
some type of scripted reel. Not
everything should be scripted. The
camera should capture moments that are
already happening and that's how you get
the most authentic version of yourself.
So how can you replicate a video like
this? It's very very simple. So this is
what I call an I made it moment and you
want to pin this to the top of your
profile and it's basically just
showcasing a desired outcome that
everybody wants to achieve and again
it's not only your ICP but your dream
follower. And this allows you to attract
a white time and so as you can see
uh me, Josh Schang, Jake Shields
absolutely crushed it after like, "Damn,
we
1 mil, 1 mil, what?" Josh got to catch
up a bit, but that's sick, you know? And
so these videos won't be a scripted and
so it's really just capturing the of and
the authentic moments. The first step is
actually pinpointing a desired outcome
that your ICP and your dream follower
actually wants. This could be buying a
dream car, telling your mom how much you
made in a month, buying a big gift for a
loved one, whatever the case may be. And
then once you have that, you can get
into documentation. Now, the key part
here is that we want to actually make
make it authentic and we don't want to
just capture it because we want to post
it as a reel. Like that's very very
important. I don't want you guys to
artificially manufacture a video just
for it to go like go viral, you know?
Now, very important to note, do not make
your loved ones feel awkward because you
want to film the video. Make them feel
natural, get them
If they're not used to the camera, then
I'd actually argue that it's better to
film on the phone because people are
more used to the phone than anything.
It's the moment that you just really
want to be in and just fully soak in.
The post-production is extremely
important for a video like this as well.
This is the make or break for the video
since it's less scripted that you want
to take more of a raw approach and make
sure that the message is not lost within
the video.
So, these are the two main aspects of
the post-production that you actually
need to consider, the clipping and the
hook. Now, the clipping is focus on
removing the least engaging parts and
the actual fluff to make sure that the
retention of the video actually does
well.
And so, this is add to the main message
of the video and if I remove this, will
it impact the video? If the answer to
both of those questions is no, then you
remove that part of the clip because it
is fluff. And so, we have an entire SOP
on it uh for our for our clients and our
editors. And then the hook, this is the
one key factor that separates the best
performing videos. I want you to
essentially make sure that you have
three hooks, a title hook, visual hook,
and a verbal hook. And so, the title
hook literally just shows like it sparks
curiosity. Before I'm even speaking, if
we didn't have a title hook, that video
would not have performed. The visual
hook was me literally on a call with her
and then the verbal hook was literally
me about to tell her something. And so,
with a combination of all three, that
video is guaranteed to perform. If we
didn't have one of the three, let's say
we didn't have the title, people would
be confused with what video it was and
they would have scrolled off. So, you
need all three. Make sure that you're
giving your editor a bunch of reference
videos, all of this, and making sure
that you're editing this as best as you
possibly can, especially since it's a
special moment that you can look back
on.
Second video, let's get into it. This
one was a fun one. Here's how I spent my
$311,000 paycheck last month. First
things first, I spent $50,000 on index
funds. I spent $21,000 on the remaining
3 months of this apartment lease. I
spent a total of 35K on mentorships and
coaching. I gave my mom and family
$24,000. All right, so this is a video
that I actually took inspiration from
from another creator. I remember when I
first watched the video that he posted,
I was literally thinking to myself like,
"What the fuck?" Like that was my first
initial reaction. It made me feel a very
strong emotion towards the video because
I was a bit, you know, confused on why
he would spend his money this way.
That's his lifestyle, that's his thing,
but I felt an emotion and usually when I
feel emotions to something, that's a
really strong idea and so I saved it to
my swipe file. Every time he would rip a
video, it'd be a 10x outlier, so I knew
I had to do it. I knew I could create
some type of twist on it to make it my
own and make it feel different. This
video was doing very, very well and it's
made him a lot of money. So now let's
get into why it actually works. In
literally the last video I was breaking
down the visual verbal hook and
everything. The visual hook is extremely
strong because you're wondering like,
"Whoa, this guy's in a high-rise?"
Big number on the screen, curiosity
loop, right? And then the verbal hook is
even stronger. Here's how I spend my
311K paycheck. The combination of the
visual hook and the verbal hook made the
video and the fact that it was hard to
replicate was the cherry on top. Not a
lot of people can say that they have
this paycheck. Not a lot of people could
say that or film in a high-rise. Not a
lot of people could have that big number
as the visual hook and so everything
tied together just made it a very, very
perfect strong opening hook. And the
goal of these hooks is to create a
massive open loop. And this is basically
just get getting you to think about
questions, getting you to think about
things in general. So I'm breaking down
my paycheck and as you're doing that,
you're wondering, "What does this guy
do?
What is he selling? Like is he lying?
What does he spend his money on? And so
these are all questions that you're
coming up and really, really good visual
hooks and verbal hooks don't just create
questions on what the video is about,
they create questions on things that are
that I'm not even talking about in the
video. And so it is this video is not
about what I do, but it creates that
question. This video is not about what
I'm selling, but it creates that
question. And even like
how old is this guy is another one,
right?
And so that creates another question. So
because there's so many open loops,
that's why the video performed well.
Again, this is the top of funnel that
would make people curious regardless of
whether or not they were ICP and if they
were even a dream follower. So because
of all of these open loops, that's why
the video worked well, but again, you
don't just want to copy different
creators and just call it a day. And so
his video was very fundamentally
different because he showed um him
buying a bunch of cars, his, you know,
like apartment rent, which was really,
really expensive. He showed
um like his lifestyle, right? Like how
much he spent on his birthdays and
everything. And again, there's nothing
wrong with that. Like I'm sure at a
certain point I'm going to be like I'm
going to be spending money on all of
this as well, but I took that and I made
it my own.
And so how did I make it my own? I
essentially asked myself, why did my
clients choose me over every single one
of my other competitors? And I distill
that messaging. And I found out that
people like me because I wasn't that
materialistic. I think very long-term
and so I invested a lot of money. I'm,
you know, consistent and disciplined.
And I basically like this is the
opposite of everything over here. Like
this was not me. And so I didn't want to
create the same video and act like I'm
spending a lot. Let me just completely
flip the narrative and literally show
how little I spent on lifestyle and how
much I spend on growing my wealth and
growing my company. And so the key with
this video was I took a format that
worked, I understood how I could
actually have that twist on it, and I
made it different. And so I found the
format that was already proven that has
already gone viral, and I just made it
my own and made it different based on
why my clients chose me, and that's why
the video actually performed extremely
well. The key thing here is that you
want to be
very, very specific. Now, what do I mean
by this? I don't want you to just
generically say what other people are
doing. If you look at the top personal
brands, like they do the opposite. And
so if everyone's going to the left, like
ask yourself, how can you go to the
right? How can you just be different?
How can you literally do this? And so
with my marketing, I knew that everyone
in my industry that was making the
amount of money that I made was selling
with a lifestyle. They were showing the
cars that they were buying. They were
showing the expensive things that they
were buying. Again, there's nothing
wrong with that. I I'm not sitting here
and saying like, oh, this is how you
should spend your money. I'm just
showing you like, what is my stance? And
so I took a very, very strong approach,
and while everyone was doing this over
here and buying all the stuff and
showing all the lifestyle, I took a very
strong stance, and I was over here. I
stood out in a mark- in a industry where
everybody looked the same, which is why
those people actually resonated with me
as well. And so the best piece of advice
I can give you is don't be afraid of
people judging you when you're posting
content. You can't please everybody. So
just please yourself. Post what makes
you feel good. Post the message that you
want to actually share. Post the videos
that you actually feel like posting,
because ultimately it's your brand, and
you get to decide what you want to do
with it. Stop optimizing for the views
and the sales and all of that. Just find
what makes you different. And if you
don't know what that is, ask the people
around you what they like about you,
what they don't like about you, and
emphasize those and be more dramatic in
the content. If you paid attention to
like what I was actually talking about
in the reel, I was talking about my
index funds. Right? I was talking about
giving my family money. It's actually
funny that, you know, I'm watching that
real. I literally just gave family money
again today. Um which was really, really
nice. And it makes me just feel good,
right? And so I want to talk about that.
I want to show people a different moral
compass with money. And all these
different things as opposed to things
that people are spending money on,
which made the video actually different,
but not just different to get views, but
to make people like me. And again, if we
go back to what the overall goal was,
it's the admirability, but then also the
likeability. And so think back to the
start of the video, this top of funnel
video hit extremely well on the
admirability because who doesn't want to
have, you know, a lot of money to spend,
but then also likeability because it
shows why you're different.
And in order to be different, you have
to be specific and be judged.
There are a lot of comments on that real
where like, "Bro, you're such a [__]
cheapskate. You're so Chinese." I'm
completely fine with that. I'm Chinese.
I'm literally, you know, I'm as Chinese
as they come. I'm I'm all completely
okay with that. I'm not trying to please
everybody. I'm just trying to please
myself, the people around me, make more
money, do my thing. I I don't care. And
so a lot of content is literally
detaching yourself from other people's
opinions of you, just doing whatever the
[__] you feel like.
It's
lol. Okay. Now, how can you replicate a
video like this? The first step is to
find out what makes you different,
right? So in a world where, you know,
basically everybody looks the same,
um there are specific reasons why people
chose you over everybody else or why
your family likes you over everybody
else, hopefully.
And you just want to find that out. And
so the best way that I can literally
give you is to hop on one-on-one client
calls.
But not just any client calls,
your favorite your favorite clients. A
lot of clients will just say, "Oh, you
know, I I bought because I really
believe that you could take me to this
desired outcome that I want to." But
your favorite clients most likely chose
you because they resonated with you on a
personal
level.
So, I would literally book five to 10
one-on-one calls with your favorite
clients and ask them questions like,
"Why did you choose me instead of the
hundreds of other competitors? What made
me stand out? Why did this actually Why
was this important for you?" Right? You
want to get to the root cause. So, if
someone says that, "Hey, um I chose you
because you were like in in my
situation, you're not materialistic."
Like, "Okay, like well, why is that
important to you?" "Because I don't
really resonate with making money for
the materialistic." "Okay, like why?"
"Because I want to make money for my
family and actually take care of the
people around me." "Okay, why?" "Because
they put me in a situation where I'm in
today. My parents were immigrants and
they moved and they sacrificed
everything to put me in a position to
succeed." "Okay, why?" And so, you get
to the real why. Like, they're not
materialistic, but their real why is the
fact that they want to take care of
their family more than anything. And so,
now you have different content ideas
that you can go off of. The key is to
dig a layer deeper and ask why until you
can't find a different answer because
every single time you ask that question,
you get different responses which will
lead to different ideas. We have a bunch
of different ways that we do this. So,
we also have like literally a client
buyer mirror form where we ask a bunch
of questions on what makes us different
and we get all of that data, we put in a
AI and it gives us a bunch of different
ideas. And then also just like
check-ins. You can ask your family
members what makes you different. Like,
just people that you really like and
resonate with.
Because again, we don't just want to
attract any client. We want to attract
people that we generally enjoy working
with. And then once you do that, I want
you to find a topic that is difficult
for the average person to replicate
because now you're creating a moat.
Like, well, why did that video perform
so well? It's because literally if you
wanted to create that video, but you
were the average person,
like it's just hard. Like, it it it
wouldn't hit the same because it
wouldn't be that big of an open loop.
And so, So what is hard to replicate,
whether it's spending a big paycheck,
investing a lot of money, buying
expensive membership, whatever the case
may be, and talk about it, right? And so
Jake did this perfectly over here, one
of our clients, Absolute G.
Um I think he's basically on track for a
six-figure month this month, which is
super sickest. He added an extra 70K
with organic content.
>> Is it a good investment to buy a nice
car at a young age? Here's what I'm
going to tell you after buying three
cars. Everyone has a mixed opinion on
it, but this is what I have to say.
Three months after launch
>> So again, the op the the hook was
perfect in a way where it's like he said
something that not a lot of people could
say,
and now he's getting into his opinion,
right?
>> my business, I bought a 2024 Mustang
GT500, brand new. Everyone told me not
to get it. I did it anyway. Then I had
it for three months, scaled my business,
and I bought a C8 Corvette. Same thing.
Everyone told me not to do it. They're
like, "You're crazy. You just bought
this car. You had it for three months."
Got the car anyway. I got it anyway. You
know why? Because I [__] earned it,
and I wanted another car. So I got
[music] it, because I can. And here's
what I'm going to tell you. When you're
young, I I think that's the best time to
get a nice car, because one, it's not
only the most impressive time to drive a
nice car,
>> [music]
>> but two, your priorities are completely
different. It It's so different when you
turn 30, and, you know, you're not
worried about a car. You're worried
about getting a house, starting a
family, all this stuff, so much more
responsibility.
>> [music]
>> But here's another thing. This car will
constantly remind you of your hard work.
All the sacrifices, everything you put
into building what you have now, to even
be able to afford this car at this kind
of age, it reminds you who you are. I
could be having the worst day ever. I
could be having the worst day, worst
week, worst month, whatever, so much
stress, so much problems going on, so
much anxiety, but you know what? At the
end of the day, I walk downstairs, I get
in this car, I get to press the start
button, I hear the engine turn on.
Instantly, I'm reminded of who the [__]
I am,
and how I got [music] here. Because 2
years ago I didn't have [__] 2 years
ago I had absolutely nothing, was broke
as [__] delivering pizza and I was
considered a college dropout. I was
considered a failure
>> [music]
>> in life and now I'm sitting in a car
that people can't even afford let alone
at a young age. I'm not saying that to
flex but you're going to [music] feel a
certain way about yourself. And that's
the thing, if you earned it and you did
it, enjoy the fruits of your labor
because you deserve it. You don't have
to prove that to anyone. [music]
Is it a good investment?
>> [__] watching that real makes me want
to buy a car. God damn.
>> [laughter]
>> But that's the perfect example of
leaning into an extreme, you know? Like
you find an open loop, you you talk
about something that not a lot of people
can talk about and then you just share
why you're different. And so this is the
like opposite of basically what I'm
going at and that's the that's the
beautiful part. Like I literally tell
all my clients lean into what makes you
different and even if it's like even if
if you're if you love cars, man, talk
about that [__] Talk about that and you
can tell how passionate he was in the
video and that's why it performed. That
that's why the video performed. He got
hundreds and thousands of views. It made
him admirable and likable at the same
time. So
it's not one or this. Like it's whatever
you feel is best. The same way that and
the same message that he's preaching in
this video. So that was the perfect
example of a spin-off on this.
Um another one is Emma. She invested in
us and this was her basically reaction
video.
>> [music]
>> That's Emma. Uh again, I I absolutely
love this video when I saw it for the
first time. I literally commented
excited to get to work and then she said
road to 100k. I saw this today as I was
actually making the script for the video
and I was like looking back at this
comment and I was so so close to 100k.
Now she crossed and she I believe she's
on track for 150 this month. Purely
organic content. Crushing it, right? And
she came at 30, so she added an extra
120k with organic content to her top
line revenue. And this is the perfect
example of, again, finding something
that not a lot of people can replicate,
showing why you did it, showing what
makes you different, and then leaning
into it to an extreme, and making people
feel like they want to resonate with you
because you stand out from the crowd.
I'm going to show you another example so
you guys can really get this idea and
really bring this point home.
>> I'm dropping another quarter million
dollars in
to the S&P 500. I'm trying to do this
basically every single month. And let me
tell you something that nobody on social
media actually will tell you.
>> So, again, big thing that not a lot of
people can replicate, and then I say,
"I'm going to tell you something that
nobody on social media will tell you."
Another open loop. And so, if you pay
attention, I actually showed quarter
mill, I showed my bank statement. So,
visual, verbal, text, everything was
there.
>> Nobody gives a [__] about the car that
you have, the watch that you have, the
lifestyle that you have except for
yourself and the people below you. When
I understood that, I stopped trying to
idolize them.
>> And then I go into what makes me
different, which is the fact that I'm
not materialistic and I'm just investing
in my future. Again,
you can see the stark contrast, but it's
just what makes you different, why are
your clients buying into you, and then
finding formats to show it. And so, I
essentially took this video, repurposed
and repackaged it into a more, you know,
nonchalant version of me filming, just
casually dropping a quarter mill uh into
S&P 500, and then just talking about
what makes me different.
This is one of the easiest formats to
run, especially if you guys are already
qualified and you guys are already um at
a high level in business. This is one of
the best videos you can rip if you're an
expert in your industry.
All right, so this is the last video
we'll review. This is [music] more of a
value talking head video about shifting
beliefs. So, let's get right into it.
Posting content in 2026 is the exact
same as investing in Bitcoin in 2013.
You will get rich for life if [music]
you do it the right way. I built a
million dollar per year business by
simply posting content, and this is the
one [music] thing that no one will tell
you. People will try to avoid building a
strong brand by running ads to grow
their business, [music] but what they
fail to realize is the person that
prioritizes the brand and their organic
marketing in the long run will always
win. Everybody is falling [music] to the
short-term solution of ads and that is
the gap that is where you can dominate
and wipe your industry. So, how I came
about creating this video was actually
very funny. Uh we were on track for a
record month and in the last 10 days of
the month, I think we closed two of 10,
which in our terms is super bad. I mean,
we were averaging like uh
usually I believe in that month we were
averaging like 70%. So, that was
terrible for us. We went on a dry spell
and the number one objection that we got
was
"I'm going to focus on paid ads. I'm
going to focus on organic later." Like
it pissed me off so bad because that
ideology doesn't make sense. It's not
ads versus organic, it's both, right?
So, because of that happening, like we
didn't hit a record month, I was super
pissed about it and I was like, "This
objection doesn't make sense." So, I was
just like I created like three reels, I
created two YouTube videos solving this
objection and soon enough we basically
we don't get that objection anymore and
it's because we intentionally remove all
of these objections by solving them in
the marketing uh so that they don't come
up again. So, I have to say this, if you
get a specific objection on a sales
call, nine times out of 10 it's because
your content failed to do its job and
your content fai- failed to actually
solve the objection, which is why your
sales rep had to actually handle it. So,
when it comes to middle funnel videos
that you post on your brand, there's
three questions that you want to ask
yourself. Number one is the limiting
belief. Is this specific video breaking
a limiting belief in my prospect's mind
that will get them one step closer
to working with me.
That is all a middle funnel video does.
The second thing is if the hook is broad
enough. And so again, what are we trying
to do? Even though it's a middle funnel
video, we can target our ICP, but can we
do what we did in the Venn diagram and
attract our ICP and our dream follower
at the same time? And then the third
question that we want to ask, is there a
clear message that I want to deliver to
basically remove the limiting belief and
change the way that they think about a
specific topic. These are the three
questions that you need to ask in order
to make sure that the middle funnel
video is actually going to be a good
fit. And the best way that I can break
this down is actually breaking down the
script with you guys, okay? The hook is
amazing. Content in 2026 is the exact
same as investing in Bitcoin in 2013.
You will get rich for life if you do it
the right way.
Amazing open loop because not only this
is applied to my ICP, but it applies to
the general public and my dream follower
because everyone knows about Bitcoin and
that's a universal term. Everyone knows
that if you invested earlier, you'd make
more money. And I basically tied my
mechanism of content to an investment
term that basically everybody knew
about. And so, even if you're not into
content right now, you would still watch
for at least 5 seconds because you're
like, "Oh, like what is this? How can I
get rich for life if I do it the right
way? What is the right way?" And so,
what do good open loops do? They ask you
a lot of questions and build curiosity
around what you're going to talk about.
And then immediately I go into
credibility. I built a $3 million per
year business by simply posting content
and this is the one thing that no one
will tell you. Again, I'm not giving the
value straight away. I'm not giving them
the information the step-by-step
straight away. I'm kind of dragging it
out a bit because no one would really
listen to me if I only if I just gave
the value straight away because they're
like, "Who are you to tell me this?" And
so, I'm essentially establishing my
authority and credibility by saying that
I built a $3 million business. And then
I call them out. Now it's going a bit
more niche. And so, people will try to
avoid building a strong brand by running
ads to grow their business, but what
they fail to realize is that the person
that prioritizes their brand in their
organic marketing in the long run will
always win. So, keep in mind, I'm using
niche keywords now that are only
applicable to our industry that our ICP
really resonate with. And so, with this,
I essentially wanted my dream follower
and the general public to keep kind of
like to keep watching. And the moment
that this that this line pops up,
they're probably gone. But guess who I
actually want to care about? I want to
care about my ICP. And so, now I don't
care about my dream follower at all in
the general public. I literally just
want to talk to the ICP completely. And
so, I'm saying key niche words, all of
that. The people that make the most
money, they don't run the best ads. Um
they have the strongest personal brands.
And when they eventually do run ads,
they can outcompete everybody because
their brand is their competitive
advantage. I'm using very, very niche
terms. And I'm using analogies that are
easy to understand because guess what?
We can assume that our Hermozis is
running way cheaper ads than your Joe
Schmo over here that that has four
followers and relies on paid ads
completely. If you run ads, you know
this that if your organic brand is
bigger, your ads will always be cheaper
because of familiarity bias.
And so, I'm talking about all this. I'm
stating the obvious. They acquire
cheaper leads and scale faster because
of the trust they build over time.
Again, that's, you know, just
essentially just shifting their beliefs.
Everyone is falling to the short-term
solution of ads, and that is the gap,
and that is where you can dominate and
wipe your industry. So, what am I doing?
I'm essentially positioning the people
that only run ads as these people that
we don't want to be. We don't want to be
the people that just run ads. If you
want to play to win, if you want to play
to dominate an industry, we can do this
instead. We're going to run ads, right?
But, we're also going to build our
organic personal brand because that's
what's going to build that familiarity
bias and that competitive advantage that
the regular ads guys can't do. So, we
essentially sent this rule out to the
people running ads in our community, and
it really hit well. And, you know,
literally, I could probably run this as
an ad, and it would do well. Now, would
I have this big of an open loop?
Probably not, but you get the idea. This
is a great middle funnel video that did
a lot of things at once. And this is how
you can script out middle funnel videos
that actually get views and change
limiting beliefs. Now, let's get into
how you can actually replicate this
video for yourself. I essentially want
you to take all of your sales calls,
Fathom transcripts, put them all into
Claude. I think this is a Claude logo,
if I'm not mistaken.
And then, basically get it to pinpoint
common objections. And essentially, what
we What do we want to do with this,
right? We want to come up with the most
common limiting belief that again, if we
remove this limiting belief, this will
get them closer
to becoming a client that we can help.
And so in my specific video,
the limiting belief was literally like
content is number one acquisition
channel. But even a layer deeper than
that,
if you want to simplify it, content is
better than ads. So basically, these are
like the core messaging that I wanted to
do. Um I lean more into this, but then
another video you'll see,
I can lean more into this where it
content and ads is the best. And so like
there's a specific core message that I
want to deliver. And again, if we go
back to the first three questions that
we asked about what makes a strong
middle of funnel video, that's what it
is. And then what I want you to do is I
want you to create a swipe file of hooks
that appeal to your ICP and your dream
follower.
Um and you can ask your clients for what
videos that they enjoy, what videos they
watch, all of that. And just build out a
swipe file, okay? And so you want to
create
a proven bank
of hooks
that are again,
ICP and dream follower. These videos
have already gone viral. And then you
want to script out the video. Now the
format when it comes to actually
scripting out the video is actually
extremely intentional. So when you're
saying the first part, let's say, you
know, we have our script over here, the
first 20% of the entire hook, right?
This needs to appeal to 100% of your
dream follower
and ICP. 100% 100%, okay? And then after
the hook, you want to actually have a
huge drop off. You want to have around
50% to your dream follower dropped off.
And then you still maintain 100% ICP.
And then over here it's like [__]
like 20%, you know, they don't even care
if if they're even still here. Again,
your ICP still super engaged.
And then at the end of at the end of it
there should be 0% of your dream
follower and 100% ICP.
So, that's essentially the structure of
your script and how you follow it. If
you look back at our script, I'm going
to put it right here, you'll see that
our dream follower was paying attention
at the beginning, but once we basically
get their initial engagement boost and
Instagram sees like, "Oh, the first 5
seconds is interesting. Let me push it
out to more people."
It'll basically push out the video to
the algorithm, which is why this video
generates 60k views, good amount of
impressions, even though it was a niche
video. And then once we use them, we can
we don't really care about the drop off.
We just want to cater to the ICP, which
is why you see that you want to use a
niche keywords after the hook.
And then you want to really shift the
limiting belief over here when there's
20% of the dream follower still paying
attention. All right? So, this is a
structure that you want to follow for
your middle of funnel content videos.
So, this video is actually a perfect
example of everything that I'm
preaching, right? Uh in the beginning of
the video, it was actually a bit more
broad. Um we were showing a bit of
animations. I already know how it's
going to be edited because I've already
done my research. We're actually taking
inspiration from Vanity Fair and how
actors react to movies. Instead of actor
reacting to a movie, it's me reacting to
my reels and breaking down breaking it
down in educational way. So, this could
have been a very very boring Loom style
video, which is a straight talking head,
but because it's packaged differently
you're you're probably still watching
because it's a different idea. You've
never seen this before with regards
you're getting so much value, right? And
so, if a person maybe wanted to post on
Instagram, even the title and thumbnail
maybe maybe a bit broader as well.
But as you go along the video, it's like
I'm covering so many niche keywords and
so many niche things in this video that
by now probably 0% of my dream follower
is still watching, but 100% of my ICP is
still watching. So, I'm literally
preaching this example live to you in
this video. If you want to break it down
and do this exercise to this video
yourself. This was a super fun video to
film, and if you want to take your
personal brand to the next level so you
can sign more clients for your business,
feel free to click the first link in
bio, watch the video on how we can
actually help you, and see if it's a
good fit. With that being said, I hope
you guys enjoyed the video, and I'll see
you guys in the next one. Peace.